scena 1
background appears
mr. engls appears: no god, pliz no!
pistolar appears: *heeh*

choices appear: 
RUN!
protecc mr. engls
distract with a noise (soundefect)


if RUN! 
roll dice and add body stat
 
if roll is 1 or 2 
[fail] 

if roll is 2 or 3
[mix success] you step on a sqirell that blows an airhorn
salmendr shots in your direction

if roll is higher than 4
[full success] get safely to the settlement
get to scene 2


{
if its [mix success]
you roll the dice and add body stat

if roll 1 or 2
 [fail] you get shot

if roll 3 or 4
[mix success] get wounded but you manage to ge to the settlement and alert everyone

if roll higher than 4
[full success] dodge the bullet and get safely to the settlement

if [full success] get to scene 2

if [mix success] get to "get that bastardo"

if [fail] get to "[fail] you are salmander`s prisoner"

}


if protecc mr. engls

 choices:
	a)grab a sharp stone and aim at the head

			b)grab a brush and put a little makeup

			c)stop right there you criminal scum!

	d)attacc

	if 
		a) roll dice and add body stat

	{if roll 1 or 2 
	[fail] get salmendr`s atention get to "salmendr sees you"


	if roll higher than 4
	[full success] you kill salmendr and mr. engls survives


	{{if [full success] get to "talk with mr. engls"}}

			{if b) or c) each character says: ..............
 
			and the following choices appear:
 
				b.a) why`d you leave the keys upon the table?

				b.b) you violated the law!}

			{{if b.a) get to "dialog with salmendr"}}

			if roll 1 or 2
			[fail] both mr. engls and you get shot
 	
			if roll higher than 4 
			[full success] salmendr obeys and you three get to the settlement

			{if [fail] get to "[fail] you are salmander`s prisoner"


			if [full success] get to "[fail] get drunk with the frogs"} -------------> DUCE LA STAGE 3
			// CONTINUARE FAIL ---> TRAIESTE SALAMANDER
			{if d) following choices appear:
					// TOATE FACE ACEELASI LUCRU
					d.a)yeet his face off
					d.b)bitchslap
					d.c)bite his toe
					d.d)kick the balls
					d.e)spit in his mouth
					d.f)reeeeeee his guts out
					d.g)swear the soul out of him
					//
					all the choices from above lead to the same thing:
 
						HA HA!


					{if roll 1 or 2
						[fail] you embarrass yourself and mr. engls gets shot


					if roll higher than 4
						[full success] you make salmendr cry, he drops the gun down}

					{if [fail] get to "[fail] you are salmander`s prisoner"



					if [full success] get to "talking with salmendr"}


if distract with a noise (soundefect)

the following choices appear:

aaa) i`ll make you an offer you can`t refuse

bbb)...if you like pina colladas 

ccc) what is love?

{if aaa) the godfather theme starts playing

if bbb) the pina colladas song starts playing

if ccc) what is love starts playing}

all choices from above get you to "salmendr sees you" and add 2 to your roll

if "salmendr sees you" roll and add communication stat 

{if roll 1 or 2
 get to [fail] both mr. engls and you get shot

if roll 3 or 4
[mix success]mr. engls gets shot, but salmendr appears to be friendly

if roll higher than 4
[full success]the shot misses mr. engls and salmendr considers you a friend}

{if [mix success] get to "talking with salmendr"

if [full success] get to "talking with salmendr"}


sdfg


 

